No.
Shen Suhe.
Are you okay?
I...
I'm fine.
I've searched here.
Nothing.
I'll go check over there.
Are you
okay, Shen Suhe?
Shen Suhe,
are you okay?
What did you
just give me?
I gave you the antidote.
Did you see anything?
No.
It's fine.
How could I suddenly be like this?
Judging from your current condition,
what you just found
should be taro powder.
We found it.
Shopkeeper,
they are right inside.
I just used
some ordinary medicinal herbs to test them.
but they didn't notice.
They must be up to something.
What
are they after?
Arrest them
and we'll find out.
Where are they?
Impossible.
I saw them come in.
This is the only entrance.
They must still be inside.
Search carefully!
We can't let them get away.
If this gets out and the Lord finds out,
we'll all be dead.
Search!
Yes, sir!
Hide here.
There aren't many of them.
I'll handle it.
No way.
You are skilled.
You must be able to escape.
I'll go hold them up.
What about you?
I have the identity of Princess Consort of Rui.
They dare not do anything to me.
They dare not do anything to you.
What about the Second Prince?
The Second Prince tried every means to get rid of you.
Isn't it like throwing yourself into the mouth of a wolf?
Wait for me.
Put this on.
You...
What are you doing?
Cover for me.
He's here.
Beat him.
I...
I'm sorry.
Mom.
I'm a monster.
My good boy.
I don't blame you.
Stop playing.
Let's go.
I can't run anymore.
Since this has happened,
we might as well report it to the authorities first.
If they go now,
they should still be able to find some clues.
Don't worry.
When we left,
I had already notified my friend in the court.
I believe
they are on their way.
In this Kyoto city,
is there anywhere you can't reach
except for the imperial palace?
[This handkerchief]
[is the same as the one used by Consort Dowager Li.]
It turns out you are not just similar to him,
you are him.
[The person who accompanied me day and night]
[after I was expelled to Lingguo Temple.]
Mr. Lou,
do you know Prince Yu?
As long as you're fine.
Great Apricot Pharmacy
suddenly exploded.
Accidentally caught fire.
The staff have all evacuated.
Exploded?
How is that possible?
We were only away for half a quarter of an hour.
It seems that
they have made full preparations.
Princess consort
You'd better go back as soon as possible
in case the Second Prince finds out something.
This is antidote.
It can temporarily relieve
the symptoms of taro powder poisoning.
Take it.
In case of emergency.
Thank you.
I hope when we meet again,
we don't
have any secrets.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Now,
he should have entered the palace.
He asked me
to tell you
to take care of
their soldiers
and their families.
What?
Great Apricot Pharmacy has always been hidden.
How did it suddenly get exposed?
I don't know where the mistake was made.
Someone reported it to the authorities in advance.
I'm worried it will involve you.
Those medicinal herbs that haven't been moved
have now been ordered to be destroyed.
All the taro powder was destroyed.
It will take a long time
to make medicine again.
Your Highness,
although the pharmacy was destroyed,
our people sent a message that
General Xiao appeared.
Now,
he may have met His Majesty.
He finally appeared.
I'll go to the palace now.
Don't worry.
In my opinion,
you'd better send the news
to Prime Minister Shen first,
and let him plead for you.
In this way,
you don't have to show up.
You can ask someone
to write more memorials
and submit them.
You're right.
If I step in now,
it might seem too hasty.
With Lord Shen's plea
and the secret letter in our hands,
my father's suspicious nature
will make him doubt Lord Shen's loyalty.
By the way,
there's another matter I must report.
This afternoon,
one of the two who sneaked into
the Great Apricot Pharmacy
is very similar to the princess consort.
Are you saying that she has been
pretending to be mad in front of me?
You go to
inform the Prime Minister's Residence
of Xiao Wei's entry into the palace.
As for Shen Suhe,
it's time for her to
play her role.
Miss.
Prince Rui.
Where's the princess consort?
She's resting inside.
Your Highness,
she's been in the chamber all day.
Yes.
She's been sleeping a lot lately.
You may leave.
I need to talk to her.
Yes.
Shen Suhe,
stop pretending.
Tell me,
where did you go today?
You don't allow me to go out.
I've never
left this chamber.
Still acting in front of me?
I'll see
how long you can keep acting.
Shen Suhe,
as long as you behave yourself,
I can ensure your safety here.
If you don't leave,
I have plenty of ways to deal with you.
[Oh, no.]
[It's taro powder.]
For years, Prime Minister Shen and Xiao Wei
have been secretly colluding with the enemy.
As the legitimate daughter of the Prime Minister's Residence,
don't you know?
Now, I want you to write everything down
in detail.
Your father is in trouble,
and you have a share of the credit.
Although she has the mind of a child,
as the saying goes,
children tell the truth.
[It turns out]
[I killed my father in my dream.]
Write it down!
Write!
Shen Suhe,
you are indeed pretending to be mad.
You may not know that
I personally presented the evidence
of Xiao Wei's treason to my father.
That secret letter
mentioned you.
Now,
if you plead for Xiao Wei in the palace,
my father will surely suspect you.
Even if your father is clean,
his followers may not be.
I'll give you one night to think it over.
Will you stay in the mansion
as my princess consort
or die with your father?
Think it over.
[Miss.]
[Is this the dress?]
[What are you eating?]
[Miss.]
Zhiyan!
Miss,
General Xiao Wei has been executed.
My father will be next.
Take this bracelet
and find a pastry stall
in the West Market
with a bamboo wind chime hanging outside.
Ask them to find Young Master Lou
and save my father.
Save my father!
What are you talking about?
Is something wrong at the PM's Mansion?
Go!
Yes.
The shop in the West Market.
Save the PM's Mansion.
How could General Xiao betray the nation?
He deserves to die.
Exactly.
How could he do such a thing?
That's for sure.
The general has committed treason.
It must be true.
Prince,
our men are ready.
We can act at any time.
With your command,
we'll save General Xiao.
[Xiao Wei,]
colluded with the enemy,
and his crimes are confirmed.
He shall be executed.
The law is clear.
You should take this as a warning,
and behave yourself.
Don't make the same mistake.
He looks like a traitor.
Look at him.
He looks like a rat.
Your Highness.
Do it.
I've been waiting for this moment.
It's time.
Execute.
How could he do this?
30 years of defending the border,
only to end up on the executioner's block.
I have served the empire faithfully
for many years.
But the heavens are clear.
I'm framed by traitors,
and died wrongfully.
The truth will come out one day.
When the enemy
comes to attack,
will you
use this sword to fight?
Do it!
What are you doing?
General Xiao,
what's going on?
I'm innocent.
Your Highness.
If we act now,
General Xiao's death will be in vain.
Since he chose to appear,
he was ready to die.
Your Highness,
we can't show up yet.
What a good general!
Yes.
I'll get back to you.
Your Highness,
someone wants to see you.
She said she was Princess Consort of Rui,
and asked you to save the PM's Residence.
Gather all shadow guards
to the PM's Residence.
Yes.
If something happens to General Xiao,
the Prime Minister's Residence will be next.
I was so eager to
find Mu Jinghao's weakness
that I forgot this.
I must find a way to get out of here.
I hope Zhiyan
is doing well.
My Lord,
General Xiao Wei defected back to the capital
and was executed.
It's said that
Prime Minister Shen is implicated,
and hasn't returned home yet.
The servant just reported that
His Highness took over the investigation
of treason against the PM.
You'll be the principal consort
in a few days.
His Highness didn't lie to me.
I bet
someone still doesn't know what happened.
Let's go
and see
how
the princess
and the prince
are doing.
The imperial guards
will come to confiscate the property
in about half an hour.
I really underestimated him.
I didn't expect him to go this far.
To take down Prime Minister Shen,
he dares to involve innocent soldiers.
If I want to overturn Xiao Wei's case,
I must protect
the Prime Minister's Residence.
What is
the Second Prince doing here?
Could it be
that he's using this opportunity
to destroy evidence and eliminate all witnesses?
General Xiao would be completely defenseless,
and the case would be irreversibly closed.
We must not let anyone in the PM's Mansion die.
If anyone dares to raid and kill,
we will immediately rescue them.
Yes.
Prince Rui,
what is your intention in leading troops to the PM's Mansion?
Just now,
General Xiao has been executed and displayed publicly.
Your father hasn't returned
since entering the palace last night, right?
What happened to my father?
Prime Minister Shen is suspected of treason
and has been imprisoned.
I'm here today
to uncover the evidence of your
collusion with foreign enemies.
My father is innocent.
He would never engage in
acts of treason for personal gain.
I'll know whether he is innocent
or not.
Search!
Yes!
His Highness ordered that
no one is allowed to enter or leave the Princess Consort's chamber.
His Highness asked you to guard her.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you stop me?
Move aside!
You are still in the mood to paint here.
You're here.
Look,
is this painting pretty?
She's really a fool.
What are you doing?
You may not be
the princess consort for long.
What do you want to do to me?
My husband won't let you go when he comes back.
We grew up together,
and have promised each other.
I should be the one
to marry into the mansion.
Why
you took everything
from me?
Today,
I'll give you back
all the grievances you've caused me.
I'll ruin your face.
Let me see who you can charm.
My Lady,
what are you going to do?